https://www.fishseekers.com/privacy-policy/

You are here:
Home »Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Fish Seekers (“Fish Seekers“) operates fishseekers.com and may operate other websites. It is Fish Seekers’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Fish Seekers collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Fish Seekers’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Fish Seekers’ visitors use its website. From time to time, Fish Seekers may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Fish Seekers also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on fishseekers.com blogs/sites. Fish Seekers only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Fish Seekers’ websites choose to interact with Fish Seekers in ways that require Fish Seekers to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Fish Seekers gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at fishseekers.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Fish Seekers are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Fish Seekers collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Fish Seekers. Fish Seekers does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Fish Seekers may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Fish Seekers may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Fish Seekers does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Fish Seekers discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Fish Seekers’ behalf or to provide services available at Fish Seekers’ websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Fish Seekers’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Fish Seekers will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Fish Seekers discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Fish Seekers believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Fish Seekers, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Fish Seekers website and have supplied your email address, Fish Seekers may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Fish Seekers and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Fish Seekers takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Fish Seekers uses cookies to help Fish Seekers identify and track visitors, their usage of Fish Seekers website, and their website access preferences. Fish Seekers visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Fish Seekers’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of Fish Seekers’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Fish Seekers, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Fish Seekers goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Fish Seekers may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Fish Seekers and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Fish Seekers may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Fish Seekers’ sole discretion. Fish Seekers encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a fishseekers.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
